<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>BruDiy</title>
    <description>Ecological and modern DIY</description>
    <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/</guid>
    <link href="http://www.brudiy.com/"/>
    <link href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/feed.rss" rel="self"/>
    <updated>2016-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Anna Llopis</name>
    </author>
    <item>
      <title>Hama Xmas Cards</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/xmas_hama_cards/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/xmas_hama_cards/</guid>
      <pubDate>2016-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/xmashamacards/01.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/xmashamacards/02.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/xmashamacards/03.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas holidays are coming and of course the celebrations to enjoy with the family and friends too… so we do not have much time to think about creative details, that's why I have prepared an express DIY that you can make easily and quickly; Christmas postcards to wish Happy Holidays in a creative and original way. It will be a little but nice gift, isn't it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this project we will use Hama beads (or plastic beads from any other brand) that we can easily find in stationeries, craft suplies stores or on the Internet. The Hama beads are very versatile and you can make a lot of creative projects with them. Usually, you have to use an specific template (there are many templates of different shapes) to create the design. These templates have little "tines" in which the beads places. For this project, I have used another method because I did not have a properly template for the tree shape… :) Ready to start?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hama Beads&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oven paper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iron&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recycled corrugated cardboard or any cardboard you have at home.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Packing tape&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scissors or Cutter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sheet to transfer the letters (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Twine (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Magnet buttons (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As I said before, I have used a different system to make the tree shape. It is not the common way but it works also. I have used tape of packing. First of all, cut a piece of tape and put it on the table so that the adhesive side is up. So that the tape doesn't move you can make a hem both at the upper and bottom and stick it on the table. On the the adhesive side we will place the beads.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once we have made the tree shape, we will cover it with an oven paper. Then we will put the iron above and we are going to make short touches so that the beads melt and they come together to each other. It is not about "ironing" the shape but rather it must be short touches (about 5 seconds) without pressing too much.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, use a recycled cardboard and cut a rectangle of 4,5 inch high x 2,9 inch wide. Here we are going to stick the tree with an adhesive double-sided tape and we will write our message to wish happy holidays. I have used a system that is a little slow but gives a very "handmade" result … It is about transfer the letters from a sheet, one by one. If not, you can always write it by hand…&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Optionally, you can add a twine to the tree or glue a magnet button to the back. Thus, in addition to offering a Christmas Card with your best wishes, you are also giving a nice detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you like it and hope you create your Christmas Cards … I'm sure you will enjoy it! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/xmashamacards/04.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/xmashamacards/05.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardboard Bear</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/cardboard-bear/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/cardboard-bear/</guid>
      <pubDate>2016-11-22T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/01.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/02.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/03.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the winter arrives, the Brown Bear of the Pyrenees hides in its lair to hibernate during the coldest months of the year. This hibernation period starts between November and December, and ends between February and April, depending on weather conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hibernation of the bears consists of a state of dormancy or winter lethargy that causes their heart rate to fall from 40 or 50 to about 10 beats per minute; The breathing rate drops by half, and body temperature is reduced from 98-102°F to 87-95°F). In addition, unlike humans, bears do not lose bone mass even when they remain immobile for about five months. The bear stops eating and maintains the functional constants thanks to the energy provided by the fat reserves accumulated during the fall, during that time the bears increase their food intake and can double their body weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bears are aware of their vulnerability during hibernation, so they dig their den or look for natural caves in the steepest and most mountainous places. The dens are hidden cavities and difficult to access where the females prepare a bed of grasses and twigs of bushes to be able to give birth to their young during that period of winter rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created this project, Cardboard Bear, few months ago and I wanted to share it … So, let's go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tracing paper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pencil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recycled cardboard (the one of the boxes of cereals goes well. It will serve to create a "mold")&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recycled cardboard (with a minimum thickness of 2mm)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scissors or cutter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brush (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paintings (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Print the templates (download templates &lt;a class="new-window" href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/myp5cvx4x3v3ph7/cardboard_bear_oso_carton.pdf?dl=0"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) and trace each piece on the cardboard of the cereals box using a tracing paper. Cut out the pieces and number each one according to the numbering indicated by the image (each piece has a number, so you will not have problems knowing which piece should fit in each slot). These pieces will serve you as a "mold" to create as many cardboard bears as you want. It will not necessary to trace the templates every time you want to create one.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once we have our "mold" templates, use them to draw the pieces on a cardboard that you like. In this case the templates are designed to create a bear with a cardboard of 2mm of thickness for this reason the slots of each piece measure 2mm.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut the pieces and place them on the table following the numbering.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can paint the pieces, on both sides, creating a unique and original design.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once the pieces are painted, it's time to mount the bear figure in 3D. It's easy and funny! ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/04.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/05.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/bear/06.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Boats</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/fishing-boats/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/fishing-boats/</guid>
      <pubDate>2015-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/01.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/02.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/03.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/04.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the port of Cambrils, a town of fishing tradition, trawlers do not go in search of fish for two months each year. It is an annual practice, usually done in May and June, consisting of a fishing ban. The ban aims to promote regeneration of the seabed, allowing species to reproduce and grow during this period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this way they are able to stabilize fishing, since it is suffering a decline in trawl catches due to banks depletion, thus increasing fish price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fishermen use this ban period for maintenance, repair and overhaul of their boats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can also make our own "Fishing Boats" with trawl included. It is a very easy project to do where we will enjoy the creativity, the sea and the beach with the little ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Corks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jute rope&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pieces of cloth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Long sticks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Silicone glue gun&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netting sachet for garlics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Screws closed circle (to make a garland of buoys with leftover corks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose 3 similar corks. It is better to use common corks of wine. Plug silicone glue gun until the glue rod is hot. Once it is ready, glue the corks as it is shown in the picture.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strengthen and decorate the boat knotting the corks with a pice of jute rope.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pin a stick as a mast in the center of the boat and at the top. The knots of the ropes should be at the bottom so they are invisible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut out a square of cloth as sail for the boat and pass it through the stick.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Now, we will make the trawl. We will use one of the netting sachet that wraps garlics. You can find it in the grocery store or supermarket. We cut the sachet in half. Now, we have a sachet that is closed at the bottom and open at the top. With a piece of jute thread, we will baste the open side of the sachet so that it closes when we pull it up from the jute thread. Then we will tie the trawl to the boat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;With the leftover corks you can make a garland of buoys. You can paint the corks to your liking and add to each a small screws closed circle as shown in the image. Then, we tie the corks together and equidistant, using a piece of jute rope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/05.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/06.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="/images/blog/boat/08.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owl Night Light</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/owl-night-light/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/owl-night-light/</guid>
      <pubDate>2015-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/19/f7/e7/19f7e7ef08e13a2540aaa6efab349525.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/d2/3d/ec/d23dec1a566666697baa6ceb404d3108.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/17/80/78/178078a9ce32c200b3075f2d88f0a402.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The owl is a bird of night life with a big head and big eyes looking forward. These eyes, perfectly adapted to the darkness, give exceptional night vision. És a stealthy and effective bird in its silent flight. Currently we can find them in every continent except Antarctica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these peculiar characteristics, it is not surprising that has been granted to the owls a magical symbolism throughout history and across cultures, becoming as the bird of wisdom, observation, protection and knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I show you the "Owl Night Light". It is about creating a small lamp that illuminates the happy dreams of the kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;White plastic bottles (recycling the bottle of the drinkable yogurt, for example)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Normal scissors or cutter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rounded scissors (also used to cut your nails)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adhesive black paper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marker&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Candle (works with button batteries and this one, in particular, makes different colored light)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We begin by thoroughly clean the plastic bottle to remove all traces of food. Then mark the outline of the bottle. To get a straight line, you can follow this trick: put the marker on top of a book, as you can see in the picture, and then, you have to go round the bottle to mark around the perimeter. More or less, the height should be about 2,4 inch (6 cm).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut the bottle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Draw the pieces of the owl on the back of adhesive black paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut all the pieces. To crop the circle of the eyes we can use a rounded scissors. To cut a round black eyes you can use a office hole punch.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once cut the pieces,remove the paper from the adhesive side and paste into our pot. To paste the eye area, we have to cut the sides of the eyes (as you can see in the picture) so you will get a good work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now all you need is to put the candle inside… so kids will have a great friend of the night! . This candle does not emanate heat so do not worry, the plastic will not melt! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/80/32/2e/80322e45b96e3aba4b9166a937993a0b.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/42/cc/c2/42ccc223a3a19eabf75cfa69c28aed8d.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/dc/b4/89/dcb489ae2528bec83c63bfd465043a5a.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/f7/06/26/f706268f0ba58b2cbf6db13535008801.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Origami conifer</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/conifer-origami/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/conifer-origami/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-12-22T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/13/6e/9f/136e9f4ac25a1f70ab749a7dfc23b271.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/be/c3/5a/bec35a511cdc184224905e28eb01e7c0.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ee/c8/cb/eec8cba8ad0c8a9f980fe9ada7a75252.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/6c/aa/c6/6caac693625288166cdb35f3cb5d6f3d.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/7f/22/d0/7f22d0d3741af774b290ab638024c509.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for simple projects to decorate the Christmas days at home, I found one that is very easy to do and it's amazing!. I'm happy to show you the "Origami Conifer".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The technique used for this project is the "origami". It is an original technique of Japan (in Japanese means "bend" (oru) "paper" (kami)) and tries to create shapes by folding paper. The only rule is that the figure should be made of one piece and not allowed to break or stick the paper.&lt;br /&gt;According to Eastern philosophy, the exercise of this handicraft brings calm and patience to those who practice it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cardstock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scissors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;We cut a square of the cardstock. The size of the square may vary but I recommend you to start with a 20cm x 20cm square as it will be easier to mark the folds. Starting from a square base folded by the middle and the diagonals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can see how to do the folds in the illustration. I have scored two ends of the square card with a geometric figures that may guide you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend the square so that the circle is on the top and the square remains on the opposite side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the left and bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn the paper, and now we work with the side where we have the square drawn. The folds will be the same. So, fold the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the left and bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The resulting shape is an elongated diamond. Cut the bottom as shown in the illustration. You'll get a triangle with 4 folds inside in both sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now you have to make cuts on both sides of the triangle, cutting the 4 folds at a time. Fold the small cuts on both sides, as shown in the illustarion, and repeat the same procedure on each fold of the tree. Once done, you will see that you have a conifer tree with 8 equal sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to start? Note that it is addictive ... There's no stop in create a lot of trees of various sizes to decorate the Christmas table, hanging on the wall or decorate a gift ... Endless possibilities! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween... Magnet Skeleton</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/magnet-skeleton/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/magnet-skeleton/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-10-22T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/31/37/ff/3137ff153bada72475ae5d42e43afb30.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/d5/76/3f/d5763f14cea2f7e9314fd9ee7da5fc4e.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/1f/e1/cd/1fe1cd02341b73c60b24178e4fc713e1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halloween! It always seemed to me so american and I have to confess that I had no idea of the origin neither I had worried to know more about it.... Great mistake!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halloween has its origins in the Samhain celebration (Celtic tradition). This celebration had held centuries ago in Britain, Scotland and Ireland on the 31th of October.  According to the ancient Celtic and Anglo-Saxon calendar, the 31th of october was the last day of the year and people used to ignite bonfires to scare evil spirits. It was thought that the souls of the dead came back to their old home looking for a body to inhabit. For that reason, people used to dress like a witch or demon, so they wanted avoid that any soul could inhabit their body. Moreover, the houses remained dark, nobody turn on any light because they were afraid that the souls of the dead found their way back home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, it was established the celebration of the "Day of All Saints" on the 1st of November and the 31th of October became in the "&lt;em&gt;Day before of the Day of All Saints&lt;/em&gt;" or what amounts to the same, "&lt;em&gt;All Hallows Eve&lt;/em&gt;", in old english.  From there emerged the word Halloween.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the United States, the celebration of Halloween Day came with the Irish immigration that are established during the nineteenth century. So I was wrong, it is not an american tradition, but rather a celtic and anglosaxon tradition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I'm living in a anglo saxon land right now (Bristol), I couldn't miss some inspiration of Halloween to share with you ! So I suggest an ecological project, fun and easy to make even with the little ones of home; The Skeleton Magnet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt; In Bristol there are a lot of typical colorful houses and I love them. For this reason I have drawn these bristolian houses in the post... :)&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/84/de/b8/84deb8c8ae4c68774cba455c11ea4f2d.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Flat stones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White paint or water resistent marker (white)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magnets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tube of liquid glue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get hold of some flat stones. :). Make sure to choose correctly the shape of the stones because you must match each of the parts of the skeleton with the stone that suits. You have to get 6 stones one for each part of the skeleton (head, body and four limbs). The stones should be flat on both sides and not very large because,otherwise, the magnet might not hold the weight. In my project, I chose a 2 inch stone for the body (ribs) of the skeleton.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paint each of the parts of the skeleton. The marker used in this project is the &lt;a target="_blank" title="http://www.posca.com/es/marcador-para-todas-las-superficies/pc-5m" href="http://www.posca.com/es/marcador-para-todas-las-superficies/pc-5m"&gt;Ecological POSCA PC5-M marker&lt;/a&gt; which is made with 41% of recycled materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When the paint is dry, you can glue the magnets on the back of the stones.The magnets should be strong and it must have enough effect to support the weight of the stones. The magnetized sheets or tape won't work because the magnetic side is not strong enough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you can already hang the skeleton in the fridge or wherever you like. BOOO! Ready to make funny your Halloween ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/fb/86/77/fb8677b5205ae5d56464b1cc1fdd0987.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/d1/23/34/d12334d924ac22d723b97ee89a3e6305.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
