<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>BruDiy</title>
    <description>Ecological and modern DIY</description>
    <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/</guid>
    <link href="http://www.brudiy.com/"/>
    <link href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/feed.rss" rel="self"/>
    <updated>2015-05-14T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Anna Llopis</name>
    </author>
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Boats</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/fishing-boats/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/fishing-boats/</guid>
      <pubDate>2015-05-14T02:00:00+02:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/85/3a/43/853a4300909a12014dc1abfa3d55fb1c.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/52/25/e7/5225e7026f2d8aa5e42f00e0ee7b643c.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/5d/8a/23/5d8a23f29751d076bfb7e925858a1e18.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ff/02/6c/ff026c34ea97d882a81f7902250d938a.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the port of Cambrils, a town of fishing tradition, trawlers do not go in search of fish for two months each year. It is an annual practice, usually done in May and June, consisting of a fishing ban. The ban aims to promote regeneration of the seabed, allowing species to reproduce and grow during this period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this way they are able to stabilize fishing, since it is suffering a decline in trawl catches due to banks depletion, thus increasing fish price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fishermen use this ban period for maintenance, repair and overhaul of their boats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can also make our own "Fishing Boats" with trawl included. It is a very easy project to do where we will enjoy the creativity, the sea and the beach with the little ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Corks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jute rope&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pieces of cloth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Long sticks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Silicone glue gun&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Netting sachet for garlics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Screws closed circle (to make a garland of buoys with leftover corks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose 3 similar corks. It is better to use common corks of wine. Plug silicone glue gun until the glue rod is hot. Once it is ready, glue the corks as it is shown in the picture.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strengthen and decorate the boat knotting the corks with a pice of jute rope.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pin a stick as a mast in the center of the boat and at the top. The knots of the ropes should be at the bottom so they are invisible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut out a square of cloth as sail for the boat and pass it through the stick.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Now, we will make the trawl. We will use one of the netting sachet that wraps garlics. You can find it in the grocery store or supermarket. We cut the sachet in half. Now, we have a sachet that is closed at the bottom and open at the top. With a piece of jute thread, we will baste the open side of the sachet so that it closes when we pull it up from the jute thread. Then we will tie the trawl to the boat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;With the leftover corks you can make a garland of buoys. You can paint the corks to your liking and add to each a small screws closed circle as shown in the image. Then, we tie the corks together and equidistant, using a piece of jute rope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/4c/9b/f0/4c9bf07d4290d07056ea0e2f4927d422.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/d8/a5/b9/d8a5b959d0c0f20a485e749c0ec0870e.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/236x/60/99/12/609912ea7a864841a05923e628e43fec.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owl Night Light</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/owl-night-light/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/owl-night-light/</guid>
      <pubDate>2015-02-05T01:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/19/f7/e7/19f7e7ef08e13a2540aaa6efab349525.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/d2/3d/ec/d23dec1a566666697baa6ceb404d3108.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/17/80/78/178078a9ce32c200b3075f2d88f0a402.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The owl is a bird of night life with a big head and big eyes looking forward. These eyes, perfectly adapted to the darkness, give exceptional night vision. És a stealthy and effective bird in its silent flight. Currently we can find them in every continent except Antarctica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these peculiar characteristics, it is not surprising that has been granted to the owls a magical symbolism throughout history and across cultures, becoming as the bird of wisdom, observation, protection and knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I show you the "Owl Night Light". It is about creating a small lamp that illuminates the happy dreams of the kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="materials"&gt;MATERIALS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;White plastic bottles (recycling the bottle of the drinkable yogurt, for example)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Normal scissors or cutter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rounded scissors (also used to cut your nails)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adhesive black paper&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marker&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Candle (works with button batteries and this one, in particular, makes different colored light)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="step-by-step"&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We begin by thoroughly clean the plastic bottle to remove all traces of food. Then mark the outline of the bottle. To get a straight line, you can follow this trick: put the marker on top of a book, as you can see in the picture, and then, you have to go round the bottle to mark around the perimeter. More or less, the height should be about 2,4 inch (6 cm).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut the bottle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Draw the pieces of the owl on the back of adhesive black paper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut all the pieces. To crop the circle of the eyes we can use a rounded scissors. To cut a round black eyes you can use a office hole punch.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once cut the pieces,remove the paper from the adhesive side and paste into our pot. To paste the eye area, we have to cut the sides of the eyes (as you can see in the picture) so you will get a good work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now all you need is to put the candle inside… so kids will have a great friend of the night! . This candle does not emanate heat so do not worry, the plastic will not melt! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/80/32/2e/80322e45b96e3aba4b9166a937993a0b.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/42/cc/c2/42ccc223a3a19eabf75cfa69c28aed8d.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/dc/b4/89/dcb489ae2528bec83c63bfd465043a5a.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;img src="https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/f7/06/26/f706268f0ba58b2cbf6db13535008801.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Origami conifer</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/conifer-origami/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/conifer-origami/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-12-22T01:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/13/6e/9f/136e9f4ac25a1f70ab749a7dfc23b271.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/be/c3/5a/bec35a511cdc184224905e28eb01e7c0.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ee/c8/cb/eec8cba8ad0c8a9f980fe9ada7a75252.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/6c/aa/c6/6caac693625288166cdb35f3cb5d6f3d.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/7f/22/d0/7f22d0d3741af774b290ab638024c509.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for simple projects to decorate the Christmas days at home, I found one that is very easy to do and it's amazing!. I'm happy to show you the "Origami Conifer".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The technique used for this project is the "origami". It is an original technique of Japan (in Japanese means "bend" (oru) "paper" (kami)) and tries to create shapes by folding paper. The only rule is that the figure should be made of one piece and not allowed to break or stick the paper.&lt;br /&gt;According to Eastern philosophy, the exercise of this handicraft brings calm and patience to those who practice it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cardstock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scissors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;We cut a square of the cardstock. The size of the square may vary but I recommend you to start with a 20cm x 20cm square as it will be easier to mark the folds. Starting from a square base folded by the middle and the diagonals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can see how to do the folds in the illustration. I have scored two ends of the square card with a geometric figures that may guide you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend the square so that the circle is on the top and the square remains on the opposite side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the left and bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn the paper, and now we work with the side where we have the square drawn. The folds will be the same. So, fold the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the end on the left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the end on the left and bend it in the reverse so that the bend remains on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The resulting shape is an elongated diamond. Cut the bottom as shown in the illustration. You'll get a triangle with 4 folds inside in both sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now you have to make cuts on both sides of the triangle, cutting the 4 folds at a time. Fold the small cuts on both sides, as shown in the illustarion, and repeat the same procedure on each fold of the tree. Once done, you will see that you have a conifer tree with 8 equal sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to start? Note that it is addictive ... There's no stop in create a lot of trees of various sizes to decorate the Christmas table, hanging on the wall or decorate a gift ... Endless possibilities! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween... Magnet Skeleton</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/magnet-skeleton/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/magnet-skeleton/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-10-22T02:00:00+02:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/31/37/ff/3137ff153bada72475ae5d42e43afb30.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/d5/76/3f/d5763f14cea2f7e9314fd9ee7da5fc4e.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/1f/e1/cd/1fe1cd02341b73c60b24178e4fc713e1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halloween! It always seemed to me so american and I have to confess that I had no idea of the origin neither I had worried to know more about it.... Great mistake!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halloween has its origins in the Samhain celebration (Celtic tradition). This celebration had held centuries ago in Britain, Scotland and Ireland on the 31th of October.  According to the ancient Celtic and Anglo-Saxon calendar, the 31th of october was the last day of the year and people used to ignite bonfires to scare evil spirits. It was thought that the souls of the dead came back to their old home looking for a body to inhabit. For that reason, people used to dress like a witch or demon, so they wanted avoid that any soul could inhabit their body. Moreover, the houses remained dark, nobody turn on any light because they were afraid that the souls of the dead found their way back home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later, it was established the celebration of the "Day of All Saints" on the 1st of November and the 31th of October became in the "&lt;em&gt;Day before of the Day of All Saints&lt;/em&gt;" or what amounts to the same, "&lt;em&gt;All Hallows Eve&lt;/em&gt;", in old english.  From there emerged the word Halloween.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the United States, the celebration of Halloween Day came with the Irish immigration that are established during the nineteenth century. So I was wrong, it is not an american tradition, but rather a celtic and anglosaxon tradition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I'm living in a anglo saxon land right now (Bristol), I couldn't miss some inspiration of Halloween to share with you ! So I suggest an ecological project, fun and easy to make even with the little ones of home; The Skeleton Magnet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt; In Bristol there are a lot of typical colorful houses and I love them. For this reason I have drawn these bristolian houses in the post... :)&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/84/de/b8/84deb8c8ae4c68774cba455c11ea4f2d.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Flat stones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White paint or water resistent marker (white)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magnets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tube of liquid glue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get hold of some flat stones. :). Make sure to choose correctly the shape of the stones because you must match each of the parts of the skeleton with the stone that suits. You have to get 6 stones one for each part of the skeleton (head, body and four limbs). The stones should be flat on both sides and not very large because,otherwise, the magnet might not hold the weight. In my project, I chose a 2 inch stone for the body (ribs) of the skeleton.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paint each of the parts of the skeleton. The marker used in this project is the &lt;a target="_blank" title="http://www.posca.com/es/marcador-para-todas-las-superficies/pc-5m" href="http://www.posca.com/es/marcador-para-todas-las-superficies/pc-5m"&gt;Ecological POSCA PC5-M marker&lt;/a&gt; which is made with 41% of recycled materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When the paint is dry, you can glue the magnets on the back of the stones.The magnets should be strong and it must have enough effect to support the weight of the stones. The magnetized sheets or tape won't work because the magnetic side is not strong enough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you can already hang the skeleton in the fridge or wherever you like. BOOO! Ready to make funny your Halloween ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/fb/86/77/fb8677b5205ae5d56464b1cc1fdd0987.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/originals/d1/23/34/d12334d924ac22d723b97ee89a3e6305.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sailor Mirror</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/sailor-mirror/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/sailor-mirror/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-07-07T02:00:00+02:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/58/87/75/58877540275a47e168d962a6709fd6d7.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/ba/7f/01/ba7f0155e38e6321c75277cd511987d2.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/bf/fb/61/bffb611f5a870c121b567c7a10d4a18c.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/16/43/5c/16435cbae6d1314582ca0e5133801530.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/8c/df/75/8cdf75b2e8a3b7936a844d890dd85042.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/e7/5c/70/e75c70b257526f0077f9263220964c59.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can restyle any old stuff that we don't want throw away. This way, we will have an original object made by ourselves, and bring back memories from the past at the same time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protagonist of this project is an old mirror with a plastic frame. It is a mirror that used to belong to M's grandmother in her home. Even though it obviously has no monetary value as an antique, after the hustle of having 
to choose from everything what is worth keeping and what is not, I had to rescue it and give it a new life for her memories' sake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;mirror&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rope&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;silicone glue gun (3 or 4 silicone glue rods)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;To give to the mirror a sailor style, we will add two nautical knots on top and bottom. To make the knots, cut 8 pieces of rope about 70 cm (4 pieces 
for each knot). As shown in the illustration (in two different colors, blue 
and black, to make it easier to understand), put two pieces on one side 
and two on the other. Then weave the ropes and finally pull the ends to shape and consistency to the knot. Save the knots for when it be time to glue them on the mirror.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Separate the mirror from its frame to work better. We are going to cover 
the entire perimeter with the rope. So put a bit of glue on the section of the frame to cover, and press the rope to fix to it. Be careful not to burn your finger because the silicone glue will get pretty hot... if you end up burning your finger, you can blow on it a bit and that's all! :)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I started with covering the mirror's frame from the inside. You have to keep in mind that the four ends of each knot will also serve to cover the frame as well. So put the knots on the mirror's frame (without glue) to calculate the spaces that we have to leave empty (where the knot and its ends will be glued) and the spaces that you have to cover to avoid that the plastic frame be seen when we glue the knots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you have calculated the spaces, you must cover inside the frame until reach to the desired height. Then, cut pieces of rope and glue them where be necessary to prevent the frame be seen once we place the knots. This step should be realized with the bottom knot as with the top one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Glue the knots and the ends. The ends of each of the knots (top knot and bottom knot) will meet in the mirror's middle, so we have to join them, trying not to get the cuts noticed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When we have glued the knots, we will be ready to cover the rest of the outer portion of the mirror's frame.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIPS AND COMMENTS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When we use a silicone glue gun, we have to keep in mind that while we 
have the glue gun plugged in, it will produce heat and the silicone rod will 
melt. Therefore, put a sheet of paper underneath the glue gun to protect the table. Also, remember to unplug the glue gun when you have to interrupt your project from time to time. If you do not, you will have the risk of the silicone rods being used up completely, and the silicone glue gun will start to burn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to share your Sailor Mirror, and send us some photos!We love the restyling!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nest Packaging</title>
      <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/nest-packaging/"/>
      <guid>http://www.brudiy.com/en/blog/posts/nest-packaging/</guid>
      <pubDate>2014-06-02T02:00:00+02:00</pubDate>
      <author>
        <name>Article Author</name>
      </author>
      <description type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/8a/ed/1e/8aed1ef2bd4e1d45f5f969469501adf7.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/d0/9a/08/d09a085b658cc14a529946d0ce557b09.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/d5/88/e7/d588e75658cfa654eaa2b199f885ad16.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/30/30/40/303040e4052a69e673b67e5ded57ddd1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ec0.pinimg.com/736x/6d/d8/87/6dd887bafcc3d7f04684a104c11b026c.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ea/00/30/ea00301073b9cabacbafadc783c35d6a.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the same topic on swallows of the past post &lt;a target="_blank" title="http://www.brudiy.com/blog/posts/movil-de-golondrinas" href="http://www.brudiy.com/blog/posts/movil-de-golondrinas"&gt;post anterior&lt;/a&gt; "Swallows Mobile", I will show you an easy project called “Nest Packaging”. It's about creating nest boxes to put delicious bombons into them. It could be an original gift for your guests and friends for those special events, wouldn't it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To do this project you can use any patterned cardboard or you can decorate 
one for yourself. I have designed, for this occasion, a pattern of swallows 
downloadable &lt;a target="_blank" title="https://www.dropbox.com/s/2yvg215ulqnxfek/envoltorio_nido.pdf" href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/2yvg215ulqnxfek/envoltorio_nido.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATERIAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;patterned cardstock (not paper, cardboard thickness is better)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white tissue paper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;scissors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;double sided tape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STEP BY STEP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, download the &lt;a target="_blank" title="https://www.dropbox.com/s/2yvg215ulqnxfek/envoltorio_nido.pdf" href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/2yvg215ulqnxfek/envoltorio_nido.pdf"&gt;template&lt;/a&gt; with the box design. You can choose to
print just the box silhouette in a A4 sheet, or printing the patterned template 
in a A4 cardstock (in this case, print in color).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cut the box silhouette.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold strongly the four sides of the box bottom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Then put the bombons wrapped in white tissue paper into the box.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Close the sides by overlapping one wing on top of the next one and so on until you get to the last one. Close the box by tucking in the last wing into the first wing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To keep the sides closed, use a double sided scotch tape and make sure that it be invisible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, you are ready to make an original and fun packaging to give bombons, candy or cookies...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would love to see your Nest Packaging project! Please feel free to share 
it, and send us some photos! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
